[[tabview]]
[[tab skull]]

----

* [*http://www.scp-wiki.net/forum/t-879617/ SCP-XXXX] - A Shoddy Knock-off

----

[[div style="float:right; margin:0 2em 1em 2em; width:256px; border:0;"]]
|||| [[image https://i.imgur.com/Rtrmtoq.jpg width="256px"]] ||
||||~ ^^SCP-XXXX-1 at the time of acquisition^^ ||
[[/div]]

**Item #:** SCP-XXXX

**Object Class:** Safe

**Special Containment Procedures:** SCP-XXXX-1 is to be stored within a standard containment locker when not in testing. All testing involving SCP-XXXX is to be held in isolated testing enclosures.

Personnel that must interact with SCP-XXXX-2 must be equipped with a full-body hazmat suit and a wireless communication system.

Due to potential infohazard, HMCL approval is required before submitting any data pertaining to SCP-XXXX to any member of the Overseer Council.

**Description:** SCP-XXXX-1 is the upper half of a human skull with various attached electronic components of unknown function, composed of impure mixtures of copper and iron, and undergoing light oxidation.

SCP-XXXX-2 appears to be a human child approximately 8 years of age, wearing a ragged hooded rabbit costume. Conscious entities which interact with SCP-XXXX-2 lose consciousness for a minimum of 3 hours. Subjects that have encountered SCP-XXXX-2 are unable to recall details about it's face, and digital analysis displays the area within the hood as either a distorted black void, or empty.

SCP-XXXX-2 always manifests outside of view of any sapient entity, generally close to SCP-XXXX-1, but has been known to manifest as far as 500 meters away. SCP-XXXX-2 only manifests during what is designated an "SCP-XXXX Event."

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Definition of SCP-XXXX Event" hide="[-] Hide Definition of SCP-XXXX Event XXXX"]]

> **1.** SCP-XXXX-1 is exposed to human blood.
> 
> **2.** SCP-XXXX-2 manifests.
> 
> **3.** SCP-XXXX-2 attempts to embrace any sapient entity able to directly observe either itself or SCP-XXXX-1, until both can only be observed through indirect sources.
> 
> **4.** [[size 96%]]All indirect sources of observation of either component of SCP-XXXX will cease to function.[[/size]]
> 
> **5.** Observation of what happens next is impossible.
> 
> **Note:** Upon completion of this event, SCP-XXXX-2 will appear to have de-manifested, and all documents and media of any kind within 50 meters of SCP-XXXX-1 will have become altered.
> 
> * 43% of all affected documents will become illegible and unreadable.
> * 56% will become unrelated to original context, but remain otherwise coherent.
> * 1% will retain original context but be altered in tone and format.

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum 1:** The following document was recovered with SCP-XXXX-1 upon acquisition, printed on a small piece of sheet plastic. It appears to be immune to the effects of SCP-XXXX Events.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Document XXXX-01" hide="[-] Hide Document XXXX-01"]]

> **Tired of //Anomalous Skulls// offered by leading brands?**
> Wish they did more than just turn things into **//Potato Skins//**?
> Well fret not, Foundation researchers! The **Cyber-Skull** is here!
> Just **[DATA EXPUNGED]** and let **Huggle Bunny** do the rest!
> 
> [[size 70%]]**Cyber-Skull** and **Huggle Bunny** are in no way affiliated with Dr. W█████████████, or other related brands.[[/size]]

The data redaction and data expungement were not added by the Foundation and appear to be part of the printing. The reverse side of this document was blank upon acquisition, but upon initial containment of SCP-XXXX-1 was found to diplay SCP-XXXX's SCP designation number.

----

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum 2:** Personnel wearing sufficient protective gear are able to interact with SCP-XXXX-2 without triggering it's anomalous effects, and were able to bring it to a secure location for interview.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Interview XXXX" hide="[-] Hide Interview XXXX"]]

> **Interviewer:** Dr. ████████
> **Interviewed:** SCP-XXXX-2
> 
> **Foreword:** SCP-XXXX-2 is restrained during this interview.
> 
> **<Begin Log>**
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Hello SCP-XXXX-2, I am Dr. ████████."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Huggle Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Uh... thank you? Are you able to tell us where you come from?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Happy Bunny Sunshine **Rainbow Land!!!**"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Okay. What relation does this place have with Dr. Wondertainment?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Huggle Bunny is compatible with leading brands!"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Uh-huh. And SCP-███? The object referenced in your label?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Cyber-Skull and Huggle Bunny are compatible with leading brands!"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "I see this isn't going to go anywhere."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Huggle Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Thank you. Are you able to tell us what relation you, as in specifically SCP-XXXX-2, have with SCP-XXXX-1?
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (distorted):** "...I'm Huggle Bunny? I Love You?"
> 
> **Dr. ████████:** "Thank you, but please answer the question?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (heavily distorted):** "...I'm ...Huggle ...Bunny!? I... Love... You?"
> 
> **Note:** The following approximate 3 minutes of the recording was replaced with a recording of person-of-interest ███████████ ██████, reading what appears to be a driving instruction manual for mooses, excerpt below. ███████████ ██████ has a tenuous grasp on human speech patterns, so dialogue will be transcribed as spoken. 
> 
> **███████████ ██████:** Place your front, little, hoovey-hooves, into, the little, hoovey-holes, on, the steering wheel. Use, your tail, to change gear. Ham sandwich.
> 
> **Note:** After the recording switched back to SCP-XXXX-2 and Dr. ████████, both remained silent for approximately 4 minutes.
> 
> **Dr. ████████ (in apparent distress):** I... I would like to end this interview now. Send in some D-Class or whatever to collect a blood sample, I--
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (distorted): HUGGLE BUNNY CAN HELP. I //AM// HUGGLE BUNNY.**
> 
> **Note:** [[size 96%]]SCP-XXXX-2 became unrestrained proceeded to waldo a knife from an umbrella muffin, and began to [DATA EXPUNGED]. Buffalo began to sing out of the car at an artichoke rainbow, until the flanges of the inert rocks was covered in █ meters of buffalo.[[/size]] [[size 0%]]**Note:** SCP-XXXX-2 became unrestrained proceeded to pull a knife from an unknown location, and began to slice at it's own wrists. Blood began to seep out of the cuts at an accelerated rate, until the floor of the interview enclosure was covered in █ meters of blood.[[/size]]
> 
> Seatbelts.
> 
> You are a cuddly giraffe, and I am huggle bunny.
> Together we can make everything better.
> 
> **<End Log>**

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum 4:** [[collapsible show="[+] Access Limited to Personnel Level 4 and Lower" hide="[-] Level 4 Security Access Granted, Squirrel"]]

> //Analysis of the rather **copious** blood sample provided by SCP-XXXX-2 have presented a genetic match for the son of O5-█, who went missing on ██/██/████. Bone sampling from SCP-XXXX-1 yields the same. SCP-XXXX was once O5-█'s son.//
> 
> //No member of the Overwatch Council is to be made aware of this. Let's just say it's an infohazard or something. Information is to be relayed to us through the HMCL. I've informed him what not to let us know.//
> 
> //We've seen what happens when an O5 gets sentimental about an anomalous object. Rampant favoritism, frequent containment breaches, inconceivable amounts of Foundation resources expended in a futile attempt to "cure" them.//
> 
> //We've seen this happen, we know how it ends. We don't need **another** one.// **-O5-██**

[[/collapsible]]

[[size 108%]]**Appendix D:**[[/size]] The data randomization effects of SCP-XXXX have been found to be "leaking" into Foundation databases and corrupting documentation pertaining to SCP-XXXX. The extent of this effect is currently contained to the random replacement of assorted words, but is to be closely monitored. In the event that documentation of SCP-XXXX becomes impossible and **Deborah, Elephants** begins to effect other documents within the database, celery explodes into bug lavae.

Shoeshine, koala. Squish, squish, squish.

Chickens is tubing soprano. Kingdom read class of penguins applesauce.[[size 0%]]Testing is to be suspended, and Keter reclassification is pending approval[[/size]]

> Requests for Keter reclassification and suspension of testing denied. SCP-XXXX is not known to possess any unique anomalous qualities, and so is not valuable enough to offset it's infohazard. It has been authorized for decommissioning. -O5-█ ##F4F4F4|Daddy...?##

**Addendum 7:** The night before scheduled decommissioning, SCP-XXXX-2 was recovered at Site-███, a facility which does not store anomalous objects, where O5-█ was residing at the time. SCP-XXXX-2 had reportedly been wandering the facility carrying a dagger, attacking all personnel it came across. SCP-XXXX-2 was detained and returned to Site-██, where it proceeded along a regular SCP-XXXX event. All documents affected in this event contained the same content.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Document XXXX-02" hide="[-] Hide Document XXXX-02"]]

> Dear Valued Customers at the Foundation, and especially O5-█, ███████ ████,
> 
> We here at data expunged apologize for your lack of satisfaction with our product. Our focus tests showed that Cyber-Skull and Huggle Bunny possessed every quality you look for in a product, but it appears we were mistaken. We would love feedback on how to improve our product, and make it worthy of your illustrious collection.
> 
> Hugs and Kisses,
> data expunged

[[/collapsible]]

[[/tab]]

[[tab marysue]]

----

* [[[SCP-XXXX]]] - He Who Punch Shark

----

Item #: SCP-XXXX

Object Class: Super Keter

Special Containment Procedures: SCP-XXXX is to be supplied with ice cream because he is the best. SCP-XXXX is to be allowed free-roam of the facility. SCP-XXXX is great and is to be sent out on a date with 105 or whatever. [Data Expunged.]

Description: SCP-XXXX is super awesome and he can punch out 682 and sharks and he is the best. Everybody likes SCP-XXXX because he is so cool and [Data Redacted.]

[[collapsible show="[Submit Login Credentials]" hide="Access Granted"]]

**Item #:** SCP-XXXX

**Object Class:** Safe

**Special Containment Procedures:** SCP-XXXX is to be contained in a standard humanoid containment enclosure at Site-17. This enclosure is to be decorated with fabricated "SCP Foundation" merchandise, which seems to cause SCP-XXXX to recognize this enclosure as it's "room."

SCP-XXXX is to be provided a laptop computer with a specially written operating system that is able to access and edit the Foundation database entry for SCP-XXXX and is able to do nothing else.

**Description:** The preceding SCP entry was found in Foundation databases on ██/██/████, and was believed to have been created by Dr. █████ until surveillance footage of  Site-17 revealed that her office had been broken into by a vaguely humanoid-shaped blob creature which was then seen using her computer. It was later recovered breaking into another office, presumably to repeat the process. This creature had not been seen before and is presumed to have only manifested just before this event. It has been designated SCP-XXXX.

SCP-XXXX possesses the ability to bypass all Foundation security protocols when using a terminal with access to the main SCP Database. At this time it has only ever been observed to edit it's own entry, and write itself as an over-powered humanoid object that enjoys ice cream and which everybody enjoys the company of. SCP-XXXX has not been known to display any of these qualities, and may not even be sapient.

SCP-XXXX frequently attempts to associate itself with other humanoid SCP objects, especially those of high value to the Foundation, and will proceed to do nothing. Most humanoid SCP objects consider SCP-XXXX's presence to be awkward, and have requested to not be exposed to it.

If SCP-XXXX goes exactly 14 hours without accessing the Foundation database, it will teleport to the nearest available terminal at Site-17. As a containment test, all terminals at Site-17 were temporarily cut from the database on ██/██/████. The resulting [DATA EXPUNGED] causing grievous harm to several SCP objects and personnel.

[[/collapsible]]

[[/tab]]
[[tab cat]]

----

* [[[SCP-XXXX-J]]] - Decattifying Chamber

----

**Item #:** SCP-XXXX-J

**Object Class:** Thaumeows

**Special Containment Procedures:** need add words

**Description:** SCP-XXXX-J appears to be a large enclosed feline litter box. When a feline entity attempts to use SCP-XXXX-J, the object will be stripped of all feline traits.

SCP-XXXX-J was inadvertently created during an experiment to create a self-cleaning cat box, when the price of cat food and cat litter became too steep for the Royal Foundation of Secret Cat Police to afford on it's limited budget during the recession. 

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Acquisition Log" hide="[-] Show Acquisition Log"]]

> **Anomalous Non-Feline Object #:** ANFO-914-CLKWRKMCHN
> **Item Description:** A pair of gear-powered chambers which reassemble the content of one chamber into the other, based on the setting of a five-way dial apparatus.

> **Researcher:** █████
> **Total Input Items:** Five (5) [REDACTED] brand Enclosed Feline Litter Boxes.

> **Input:** One (1) enclosed litter box
> **Setting:** Coarse
> **Output:** A pile of melted plastic.

> **Input:** One (1) enclosed litter box
> **Setting:** Rough
> **Output:** The disassembled parts of a [REDACTED] brand enclosed litter box.

> **Input:** One (1) enclosed litter box
> **Setting:** 1:1
> **Output:** [DATA EXPUNGED]

> **Input:** One (1) enclosed litter box
> **Setting:** Fine
> **Output:** Output object causes the hind-quarters of the subject to disappear. Object does indeed save on cat-litter and is kept in storage.

> **Input:** One (1) enclosed litter box
> **Setting:** Very Fine
> **Output:** Output object causes purgery of all feline traits of the subject. Designated SCP-XXXX-J. Experiment to save on cat litter deemed a success.

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum-XXXX-J-01:** Cross-Experimentation with SCP-XXXX-J to eliminate feline expenses approved by the MEOW5.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Experiment Log" hide="[-] Show Experiment Log"]]

> **Object:** SCP Object to be exposed to SCP-XXXX-J.
> **Description:** Description of Object.
> **Result:** Result of Exposure to SCP-XXXX-J.

> **Object:** SCP-076-2
> **Description:** A gray hairless sphynx which constantly bites assigned researchers. When terminated, emerges from SCP-076-1 unharmed. Object is not known to eat, nor produce waste, but leads to [REDACTED] costs in bandages for kitty booboos.
> **Result:** Object combusts, later reported to still be a cat. Experiment failed.
> 
> **Object:** SCP-076-1
> **Description:** A shoe-box from which SCP-076-2 emerges.
> **Note:** Nothing happened until current manifestation of SCP-076-1 was terminated.
> **Result:** Object is now a large stone box. SCP-076-2 later reported to resemble a human, and has taken to aggressively murdering personnel instead of leaving booboos. Experiment deemed successful.

> **Object:** SCP-136
> **Description:** A cat-shaped doll made of felt. Causes human subjects to perceive apparitions of an Exotic Shorthair which constantly demands to be fed.
> **Result:** Object is now human-shaped and made of clay. Apparitions now resemble a human, which does not appear to want food. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-173
> **Description:** "Ninja/Stalker Cat."
> **Result:** Object is now a statue and does not eat. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-426
> **Description:** A grey tabby which causes personnel to refer to myself as a cat.
> **Result:** I am now a toaster and do not eat nor produce waste. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-662
> **Description:** A silver can-opener that when used to open a can of cat food, summons a "tuxedo" cat, designated SCP-662-1. SCP-662-1 appears to be trained and will obey any command issued to it, except commands to stop being a cat.
> **Note:** SCP-662-1 instructed to take SCP-662 into it's mouth and enter SCP-XXXX-J.
> **Result:** SCP-662-1 combusts. SCP-662 now appears to be a hand bell. SCP-662-1 now appears to be a human butler which calls itself "Mr. Deeds." When questioned about his time spent as a cat, SCP-662-1 appears agitated and is unable to respond. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-682
> **Description:** Omnicidal Egyptian Mau, female, which adapts to all termination attempts. Object features assault rifle taped to fur. Object consumes $██████ in cat food per month, and [DATA EXPUNGED] in litter.
> **Result:** Object is now a reptile and has shed it's assault rifle. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-933
> **Description:** A roll of Duct Tape which when applied to the face of a human subject and removed, causes the subject's face to be replaced with the face of a cat.
> **Note:** SCP-933 is hung by a chain from the neck of a common house cat.
> **Result:** SCP-933 now no longer replaces the subject's face with anything. Experiment successful.

> **Object:** SCP-963-1
> **Description:** A white-gold medallion in the shape of a cat face, with a ruby for a nose. Living subjects that come in contact with SCP-963-1 believe they are now cats.
> **Note:** SCP-963-1 is also hung by a chain from the neck of a common house cat.
> **Result:** SCP-963-1 has became a round ornate amulet. Cat used for this experiment is now a talking chimpanzee that claims to be deceased former junior researcher Dr. Bright. All subjects previously affected by SCP-963-1 also now claim to be deceased former junior researcher Dr. Bright. Deceased former junior researcher Dr. Bright has been noted to consume less resources than a cat, but the immediate cost of cleaning the corpses of the spare Brights negated any saving. Experiment failed.

> **Object:** SCP-███-3
> **Description:** [DATA EXPUNGED]
> **Result:** Subject is no longer cats. Experiment successful.

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-J-02:** Exposure of SCP-511 to SCP-XXXX-J resulted in [DATA EXPUNGED]. It has been decided that roughly 2% of all SCP objects will remain cats, to prevent further [EXPUNGED].

[[/tab]]

[[tab tale529]]

----

* [[[The Half Truth]]]

----

> ++++ SCP-004: Appendix C
> **Date of Discovery:** ██/██/████
> 
> Other half of [[[SCP-529]]] found inside [[[SCP-004]]]-1. Tests are being run to see how the rear end of Josie the Half Cat ended up in this dimensional pocket.
> -[REDACTED]

> **SCP-529: Addendum #1**
> On ██/██/████, the second half of SCP-529 (SCP-529-B) was found inside SCP-004. How it ended there is unknown. The half is inert as if paralyzed, but otherwise perfectly healthy. When put in its presence, SCP-529 treats it as a familiar cushion and appears to enjoy cuddling it.
> -[[[circeus-personnel-file|Agent Circeus]]]

> **SCP-529: Addendum #2**
> On ██/██/████, [REDACTED] began experiments to reunite SCP-529 and SCP-529-B.
>

Dr. Gears awoke in the chambers of [[[SCP-2000]]].

After taking a moment to regain his composure, he took a note to himself.

> Josie does NOT have a lower half.
>
> -Dr. Gears, ██/██/████

[[/tab]]

[[tab tale1926]]

----

* [*http://www.scp-wiki.net/forum/t-637979/scp-1926#post-1740607 The Needles Do Burn]

----

//We were born with one purpose. We protect everything we hold dear.//

**“[*http://www.scp-wiki.net/scp-1926 MEWTS]! READY YOUR BATTLE STATIONS! SMOGGO IS ESCAPING!”**

//Centuries we Mewts have defended everything we hold dear from Smoggo.//

**"QUODAR, COVER THAT ENTRY PORTAL! ARUBADUB, ZANZIBULE, HOLD THE DEMON BACK!”**

//Everything we hold dear has many names for Smoggo.//

**“KEEP HIM IN THE HOLE WHILE SNOOZEE CLOSES THE DIMENSION FIBER!”**

//Lucifer, Satan, Beezlebub, The Boogieman, Radical... Larry...?//

**“SNOOZEE? SNOOZEE, NOW! SNOOOOOOZEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!”**

//I failed to protect them. I failed to protect everything we hold dear.//

**“SNOOZEE!? SNOOZEE, NO!!”**

//I opened the door myself. I thought I could stop him. I thought I could finally save them.//

**“SNOOZEE, YOU TREACHEROUS BASTARD, GODDAMN YOU!!”**

//Smoggo stared at me grinning. Just stood there, staring, grinning. In the wordless thought-speak of the Mewts, he spoke to me. “Thank you, vile worm.”//

**“SNOOZEE! SNOOZEE WHY? WHY SNOOZEE??”**

//He picked me up. Smoggo picked me up. And I could feel my body begin disintegrating.//

**“WAIT, WHAT'S HAPPENING, WHAT'S HE DOING TO SNOOZEE??”**

//Smoggo just does that to things. He is the devil. He threw me aside when enough of me had burnt away.//

**“MEWTS. SMOGGO HAS ESCAPED. REPEAT: SMOGGO HAS ESCAPED.”**

//I was now a vile worm as Smoggo referred to me. Also, I now resemble a caterpillar.//

**“PROTECT EVERYTHING WE HOLD DEAR, PROTECT--”**

//They're gone now. That which we hold dear is no more. It was my fault.//

**“GODDAMN IT SNOOZEE YOU HAD ONE JOB. ONE JOB SNOOZEE.”**

//Since we were brought to this place, of cold metal, I have discovered our captors also hold [*http://www.scp-wiki.net/scp-106 Smoggo].//

**“OH GOD EVERYTHING WE HOLD DEAR. EVERYTHING WE HOLD DEAR IS BURNING.”**

//I thought that they could forgive me. They could forgive me now that Smoggo is contained.//

**“WHY IS EVERYTHING ON FIRE. THE LANTERNS?? SMOGGO MELTED THE LANTERNS.”**

//But they can't contain Smoggo here. Only we could keep Smoggo contained. Could. In the past.//

**“They're gone... They're all gone... Everything we hold dear... They're all gone...”**

//Smoggo cannot be stopped. I let this happen. I made it happen.//

**“Damn you Snoozee... damn you... Damn You SNOOZEE!!”**

//I thought I could stop him. I thought I could save them.//

**“YOU. ARE. ETERNALLY. BANISHED. FROM. HAPPY FUN TIMES.”**

//I'm so sorry. I could not protect everything we hold dear.//

//They leave me like this. They can restich my body. They do not.//

//The needles they put in my head are not enough. I deserve much worse.//

[[/tab]]

[[tab Notes]]

+ Notes and SCP ideas

* Photo that inspired Happy Bunny was taken with my cellphone while on a cruise. There was a kid walking around the ship in a bear or bunny costume (I don't remember but I hope it turns out to be a bunny, obviously) and they were in the photo, and for some reason you couldn't see their face, and everything else in the picture was distorted, it was really cool. It's probably still on that phone, and I'm pretty sure I still have it, otherwise it seems to be lost.

[[div style="float:right; margin:0 0em 0em 1em; width:250px; border:0;"]]
||~ [[image https://i.imgur.com/G3pcqJ5.jpg width="250px"]] ||
||~ **I have this VHS tape. ||
||~ I don't know what's on it. ||
||~ I don't know what the label means. ||
||~ I don't know where it came from. ||
||~ I must make it an SCP somehow.** ||
[[/div]]

* "Brain Thrower. A World War II era flame thrower that shoots human brains. Lead to a very confused squadron." I have no strong emotional attachments to this so if I can't figure out what else to do with it that can make it an SCP, I'll just make it an Anomalous Object and be done with it.

* Drunken researcher randomly decides to go out drinking with 890. 890 agrees, but only after the researcher drunkenly offers to cross-test it with various machine SCPs. Wacky hijinx ensue. And then it gets dark.

* I am a Toaster and You are a Fish need to cross paths.

* "An abandoned coal mine found deeper than humans have ever been known to explore." The inspiration for this is obvious. Should be workable.

* Cow burning, religious sacrifice. Foundation, your IRC is weird and I love it.

* "An animated sapient statue of John Lennon, powered by widespread belief in the ideals of communism. Currently Neutralized." Can't decide whether to make this guy exactly like John Lennon, or make him a really nice guy you kinda feel bad for in the end. *shrugs* I don't know that much about communism but I really liked the idea.

* 682 is run through 914 for some reason and becomes The Hateful Star. The Hateful Star in Foundation Containment, it turns out, is a temporarily displaced 682. This idea makes no sense, but neither does The Hateful Star.

* "A Las Vegas Transit Bus which compels passengers to never want to leave. Passengers will continue to desire to want to get to their destination, but will refuse to leave when prompted. They will show irritation as the hours, days, or even years go by, but they will continue to act as though this is a normal bus ride." I was on a bus once with a person, we both knew we'd be on the bus for just a few minutes, but they were really impatient, and I'd been putting up with their crap all day, and it was annoying. I wished that bus ride would never end, just to make them unhappy.

* "A cartoon pizza, that once you see it, you become unable to physically taste pizza. Upon seeing an image of a pizza, you will taste the pizza."

* Todd in the Shadows as a Joke SCP.

* Twitter as a Joke SCP.

* A tale in-which the SCP Foundation is called to rescue a non-anomalous cat in a tree.

* A reality-warper with a blacked-out 4 letter name visits the Foundation requesting the return of his toys. He is terminated quite easily.

* A tale in-which 682 is finally terminated (No specific method will be given and the researcher who had the honors will be un-named) and the Foundation must deal with the possibility of losing the funding they were being specifically provided for the containment of 682.

* 248/2599

* The first Michael Jackson song I ever heard was "Ghosts." Michael Jackson was announced dead the following morning.

* 148/1968

* "Union of Concerned Bacon-Squirrels. A unionized community of squirrels which appear to be made out of bacon. Direct interaction with them provokes subjects to no longer perceive or believe in the existence of squirrels. Research into the anomalous effects of this SCP is impossible at this time, but does not appear to be memetic, as it is possible to know that it exists."

* What if the founder of Dr. Pepper was The Administrator?

* SCP-2006 finds itself amidst a massive containment breach and believes the work of widespread terror and chaos caused by other SCP objects to be the work of amateurs, eventually growing bored with how much attention and "fake" scares the likes of 106 are getting, and starts just beating the crap out of them to get them back in containment so it can be the center of attention.

> Too Spooky watched from a distance as the lizard ate through a screaming group of researchers.
> 
> "Pffft," he scoffed to himself. "Gore? Really? That's not scary. That's just gross. You want to scare some scientists you pop up from behind a wall and yell, 'boo!' Eating your audience is just bad showmanship. Amateurs."
> 
> The door to Too Spooky's side started to corrode. It opened and the grinning old man emerged.
> 
> "Now you, you got the right idea. Chilling entrance, ominous build-up. But what's with the naked hobo routine? You look like you're covered in blood, that's a nice touch, but-- Hey are you listening? Hey. Hey, Radical Larry. Hey. Hey. Heeey."
> 
> The Old Man was ignoring the annoying gorilla robot deep-sea diver television set... thing. He didn't pay attention to alot of things anymore. He only payed attention to scared scientists. And the orange ones. But he was interrupted in his old thoughts when the monkey thing grabbed his shoulder and turned him to face itself.
> 
> "I am so SICK AND TIRED of being ignored today!! I'm scary darn it!!" Too Spooky said, as he punched the old man in the face.

> **I don't remember the context of this conversation. 
> It probably had to do with Clef's Proposal and Bullet Cat.**
> "This is like the birth of Christianity."
> "Only cooler, and with cats made out of sentient bullets!"
> "Just like Mommy used to makes."

> **I read the comma aloud while reading a Tale to a friend. This happened.**
> "Agent Comma. He makes the best Toast."
> "Have some delicious Toast."

> A hairbrush, that when held, causes nobody in the world to be able to die.
> A hairbrush that brushes away memories.
> A hairbrush that makes you think hairbrushes are anomalous.

> **[*http://www.reddit.com/r/SCP/comments/297ph1/are_201_and_648_related_to_each_other/cii9pyn Post] in a Reddit Thread about relations between 201 and 648**
> "As MTF-## was exploring SCP-####-1, they encountered the lost D-Class D-XXXX from SCP-XXXX-1 Exploration Log 01. Upon pleasantries, SCP-507 suddenly materialized (and was confirmed to have de-manifested from our own native space) and was confused to find itself in the presence of familiar faces. SCP-1985 then also manifested. General confusion was experienced by all, until it was decided that evacuation was in order."

[[/tab]]

[[/tabview]]