Experiment #: ███
Name: Dr. Something.
Test: With HMCL approval, Dr. Person provided with a blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1, and a copy of Interview XXXX-01.
Result: Dr. Person loses consciousness for 27 hours and reports uncharacteristic love of children. Provided copy of Interview XXXX-01 completely unchanged and is the second reported instance of a document that was left unaltered by SCP-XXXX. Dr. Person later found to have a watermark-like overlay of what appears to be SCP-XXXX-2 imprinted on both of subject's eyes.
Note: Genetic information can apparently be affected by SCP-XXXX.

Experiment #: 365
Name: Dr. Something
Test: D-XXXX-██ provided a copy of the ██/██/████ issue of █████'█ █████ magazine, and a blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1.
Result: D-XXXX-██ fails to regain consciousness before monthly termination. Reports from D-Class not considered high priority, and termination is carried out as normal. Content of provided document now appears to match the driving manual read during Interview XXXX-01, up to page 26.