[[tabview]]

[[tab scp_skull]]

* [*http://www.scp-wiki.net/forum/t-879617/ SCP-XXXX] - A Shoddy Knock-Off

----

[[include component:image-block name=https://i.imgur.com/Rtrmtoq.jpg|caption=SCP-XXXX-1 at the time of acquisition]]

**Item #:** SCP-XXXX

**Object Class:** Safe

**Special Containment Procedures:** SCP-XXXX-1 is to be stored in a standard containment locker. Testing of SCP-XXXX is to be conducted only in isolated testing enclosures and are to be observed remotely. Only Class D Personnel may interact with SCP-XXXX-2 directly. If other personnel must interact with SCP-XXXX-2 are to be equipped with full body protective gear, opaque goggles, and a digital guidance system.

**Description:** SCP-XXXX-1 is the upper half of a human skull with various attached electronic components. Research is on-going as to the exact purpose of these components, but it is believed that they serve some function in the anomalous properties of SCP-XXXX.

* Gear-shaped dial made of mixed copper and iron embedded in the right orbital region. Believed to be used for adjusting the effects of SCP-XXXX, but does not appear to be functional.

* Round copper mechanism grafted onto the left orbital region, attached to steel tubing which runs through the neuro-cranial cavity, held in-place by copper plates bolted onto the sides of SCP-XXXX-1. Believed to be linked to the ability of SCP-XXXX-2 to seemingly know exactly where SCP-XXXX-1 is at all times.

* Seemingly random bits of copper and iron plates along the top of SCP-XXXX-1, centered around a large copper gear around the symbol of **[Data Expunged]** engraved into the bone. Research into the function of these mechanisms requires approval by O5-██.

* Two bolts implanted on the right side of the forehead. Purpose unknown.

* Two metal plates between the orbital regions. Purpose unknown.

When SCP-XXXX-1 is exposed to human blood, SCP-XXXX-2 manifests in a nearby location, outside of view of any sapient entities. SCP-XXXX-2 appears to be a human child, estimated to be █ to ██ years of age, wearing a hooded brown rabbit costume. Any entity that directly observes SCP-XXXX-2 will experience affection towards it, regardless of any previously held dislike of children.

After SCP-XXXX-2 manifests, it will begin to attempt to embrace any sapient entities able to directly observe itself or SCP-XXXX-1. Conscious entities that interact with SCP-XXXX-2 lose consciousness for a period of at-least 3 hours. No subject to survive an encounter with SCP-XXXX-2 has been able to recall details about the object's face, and digital observation of the area within the hood of SCP-XXXX-2 has been inconclusive, often being distorted or blurred.

Once neither component of SCP-XXXX is able to be directly observed, all sources of digital observation will momentarily cease function, SCP-XXXX-2 will appear to have de-manifested, and all media and data of any kind within ██ meters of SCP-XXXX-1 will have become altered.

* ██% of affected documents consist of content unrelated to the document's original context.

* ██% of affected documents become scrambled, resembling glitches in a computer system.

* █% of documents retain original context, but will be altered in tone and format.

**Addendum XXXX-01:** The following document was attached to SCP-XXXX-1 upon initial acquisition by the Foundation, printed on a small piece of sheet plastic and tie to the right orbital implant via string, and appears to be immune to the data randomization effects of SCP-XXXX:

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Document XXXX" hide="[-] Hide Document XXXX"]]

> **Tired of anomalous skulls offered by leading brands?**
> Wish they did more than just turn things into potato skins?
> Well fret not, Foundation researchers! The **BRANDNAME Cyber-Skull ®** is here!
> Just **[Data Expunged]** and let the **BRANDNAME Happy Bunny ®** do the rest!
> 
> [[size 75%]]**Cyber-Skull** and **Happy Bunny** are Registered Trademarks of the Mr. BRANDNAME Company. 
> The Mr. BRANDNAME Company is in no way affiliated with Dr. W█████████████ or related brands.[[/size]]

It should be noted that the black-boxing and data expungement were not added by the Foundation and appear to be part of the printing.

----

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-02:** Personnel wearing sufficient protective gear and blinders are able to safely interact with SCP-XXXX-2 without triggering it's anomalous effects, and with the help of digital guidance systems, were able to apprehend SCP-XXXX-2 and bring it to a secure location for interview.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Interview SCP-XXXX" hide="[-] Hide Interview SCP-XXXX"]]

> **Interviewer:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1
> **Interviewed:** SCP-XXXX-2
> 
> **Foreword:** Interview conducted with Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 blindfolded and separated from SCP-XXXX-2 by a glass wall. Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 took an interest in SCP-XXXX-1 after seeing the object, but is is not fond of children and was not aware of SCP-XXXX-2. Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 was chosen to conduct this interview so that the psychological effects of SCP-XXXX-2 could be more closely observed.
> 
> **<Begin Log>**
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "OK, Let's get this started."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Of-course you do. Anyway, where do you come from?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Happy Bunny Sunshine **Rainbow Land!**"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Okay. And what does Happy Sunshine Whatever Land have to do with Dr. Wondertainment?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (distorted): "BRANDNAME HAPPY BUNNY IS A REGISTERED TRADEMARK OF THE MR. BRANDNAME COMPANY AND IS IN NO WAY AFFILIATED WITH DR. WONDERTAINMENT OR RELATED BRANDS.**"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Yep, I read the label. Fine. What relation does SCP-XXXX-1 have to SCP-███?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2: "BRANDNAME CYBER-SKULL IS COMPETITIVE WITH LEADING BRANDS!** I'm Happy Bunny, I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "......Ugh, Can I get a drink in here? //Please?//"
> 
> **Note:** A member of security personnel, also blindfolded, entered the interview enclosure to provide Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 with a drink, and was instructed to remove his blindfold.
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1: "WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU--** ......OH-EM-GEE, HE'S SO CUTE!"
> 
> **Note:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 proceeded to embrace the glass wall between himself and SCP-XXXX-2.
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1: "I LOVE YOU TOO HAPPY BUNNY, I WANNA GIVE YOU A HUG!"**
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2: "YAAAAAY!"**
> 
> **Note:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1's blindfold was replaced, and the member of security personnel exited the enclosure.
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1: "WHAT THE //[Expletive Redacted]// DID YOU DO TO ME??"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "NO. NO YOU'RE NOT YOU ARE A KID, //IN A COSTUME//."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (slightly distorted):** I'm... Happy... Bunny...? I... Love--?
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "You, are **just another human**, that some sick **toy company** has abducted and brainwashed, just like **ALL THE OTHERS WE HAVE.**"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (heavily distorted): "BRANDNAME HAPPY BUNNY IS A REGISTERED TRADEMARK AND PATENT OF THE MR. BRANDNAME COMPANY AND IS IN IN NO WAY DERIVATIVE OF EXISTING PRODUCTS FROM LEADING BRANDS.**"
> 
> **Note:** The next █ minutes of the recording were seemingly replaced with a recording of person of interest ███████████ ██████ reading from a driving manual for mooses. Below is a excerpt from the reading. ███████████ ██████ has a tenuous grasp on human speech patterns and dialogue will be presented as spoken.
> 
> **███████████ ██████:** Place your front, little, hoovey-hooves, into, the little, hoovey-holes, on, the steering wheel. Use, your tail, to change gear. Ham sandwich.
> 
> **Note:** After the recording switched back to SCP-XXXX-2 and Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1, both remained silent for █ minutes.
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 (in apparent distress):** I... I would like to end this interview now. Send in some D-Class or whatever to collect a blood sample, I--
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (heavily distorted): HAPPY BUNNY CAN HELP. I //AM// HAPPY BUNNY.**
>
> **Note:** SCP-XXXX-2 proceeded to waldo a knife from an umbrella muffin, and began to sentimentality it's own wrists. Buffalo began to sing out of the car at an artichoke rainbow, until the flanges of the inert rocks was covered in █ meters of buffalo. [[size 0%]]**Note:** SCP-XXXX-2 proceeded to pull a knife from an unknown location, and began to slice at it's own wrists. Blood began to seep out of the cuts at an accelerated rate, until the floor of the interview enclosure was covered in █ meters of blood.[[/size]]
> 
> Seatbelts.
> 
> You are a cuddly giraffe, and I am a happy bunny.
> Together we can make everything better.
> 
> **<End Log>**
> 
> **Closing Statement:** Despite successfully demonstrating the effects of SCP-XXXX-2, Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 is to be reprimanded for allowing his personal dislike of children to lead to unprofessional conduct in handling SCP-XXXX-2.

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-04:** [[collapsible show="[+] Access Limited to Personnel Level 4 and Lower" hide="[-] Level 4 Security Access Granted, Squirrel"]]

> //Analysis of the **copious** blood sample provided by SCP-XXXX-2 during Interview XXXX has presented a 100% genetic match with the son of O5-█, who was reported missing on ██/██/████. Bone sampling of SCP-XXXX-1 yields the same.
> The Overwatch Council is not to be made aware of the results of genetics testing involving SCP-XXXX, least of all O5-█. We've seen what happens when a council member associates closely with an anomalous object; confusing it for a loved one and such. Rampant favoritism, frequent containment breaches, and inconceivable amounts of Foundation resources exhausted in futile attempts to "cure" them. We've seen it all before. We know what happens. We don't need another one.// -O5-██

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-05,000,000,000:** The data randomization effects of SCP-XXXX has been found to be "leaking" into Foundation databases and corrupting documentation pertaining to SCP-XXXX. The extent of this effect is currently contained to the random replacement of assorted words, but is to be closely monitored. In the event that documentation of SCP-XXXX becomes impossible and **Deborah, Elephants** begins to effect other documents within the database, celery explodes into bug lavae.

Shoeshine, koala. Squish, squish, squish.

[[size 0%]]Testing is to be suspended, and Keter reclassification is pending approval.[[/size]]Chickens is tubing soprano. Kingdom read class of penguins applesauce.

> Requests for Keter reclassification and suspension of testing denied. SCP-████ was discovered and contained due to SCP-XXXX turning a copy of it's own documentation into a copy of **[Redacted]**. We can can utilize this.
> 
> Besides, it's not like this is the worst info hazard we have. -O5-█

[[collapsible show="[+] Experiment Log XXXX" hide="[-] Exper...I love you!...XXXX"]]

> **Experiment #XXXX-001:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME2
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-001
> **Items Provided:**
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for approximately 6 hours and later reports discomfort considered typical of sleeping on the floor of a Foundation testing chamber. The labels on D-XXXX-001's standard Class D Personnel uniform now read as different labels, including one printed in Swahili for Mr. BRANDNAME branded snackfoods on D-XXXX-001's pants.

> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 copy of the Foundation documentation for SCP-XXXX.
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for 18 hours and later reports feeling well rested despite having a bad dream. Provided documents now appear to be documentation for non-existent SCP-████, complete with acquisition logs and containment procedures. SCP-████ is later acquired in exactly the incident described by the given acquisition log, and is contained in the same way. Researchers writing the official Foundation documentation for SCP-████ wrote a duplicate of the documents provided by SCP-XXXX as their first draft, without prior knowledge of SCP-XXXX.
> 
> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 Copy of the novel "███ █████████ ████, ████████ █████ ████ █████ ██ ████ ███-███ ███████████ ███ ██████"
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for 4 hours and reports a slight headache. Provided document is found to have become a french picture book appropriate for a standard child's reading level, containing various collages of every visual memetic kill agent known to the Foundation, and was immediately disposed of via incineration.
> 
> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 phone book.
> * Blood sample from SCP-XXXX-2, to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result: [Data Expunged]** 
> **Note:** Further testing by this researcher is forbidden by order of O5-██.

> **Experiment #XXXX-365:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME2
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 copy of the ██/██/████ edition of █████'s █████ magazine.
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject fails to regain consciousness before monthly termination of D Class Personnel. Provided document now appears to match the driving manual read by ███████████ ██████ during Interview XXXX, up to page 27.

[[/collapsible]]

[[/tab]]

[[tab Notes]]

+ Notes and SCP ideas

* scp_skull represents my first (two) inspiration(s) for an SCP and my first serious idea for what to write about here and it means alot to me. I reject the idea of it not being my first SCP, no matter how good any of my later ideas are, and I will do whatever it takes to make a skull that summons a bunny that everybody likes who rewrites stuff, into an interesting SCP. I have made a serious mistake.

* Photo that inspired Happy Bunny was taken with my cellphone while on a cruise. There was a kid walking around the ship in a bear or bunny costume (I don't remember but I hope it turns out to be a bunny, obviously) and they were in the photo, and for some reason you couldn't see their face, and everything else in the picture was distorted, it was really cool. It's probably still on that phone, and I'm pretty sure I still have it, otherwise it seems to be lost.

[[include component:image-block name=https://i.imgur.com/3LEV3zl.jpg|caption=I have this VHS tape.
I don't know what's on it.
I don't know what the label means.
I don't know where it came from.
I must make it an SCP somehow.]]

* An SCP just appears in the database one day. It's an indestructibe reality-warper that punches 682 out and punches sharks with ice cream and everybody likes it. It's actually a vaguely-humanoid blob thing that does none of those things, doesn't make you like it, doesn't say or do anything except try to "hang out" with "popular" SCPs and personnel, and it's only anomalous quality is an unstoppable ability to edit it's own entry in the SCP database, save for addendums, which it ignores. It appears to be otherwise non-intelligent and non-sapient.

* "Brain Thrower. A World War II era flame thrower that shoots human brains. Lead to a very confused squadron." I have no strong emotional attachments to this so if I can't figure out what else to do with it that can make it an SCP, I'll just make it an Anomalous Object and be done with it.

* "De-Cat-ifying Chamber: A chamber which turns cats into things that are not cats." I said once I had no intention of making an SCP that was a cat at this time despite being a cat myself, and I meant it. This SCP is __so__ not a cat, it de-cats other cats. Will probably be a Joke SCP with a canon stating that originally, most SCP objects were cats, as opposed to the roughly 2% cats are currently, and they were de-cat-ified to break up the monotony. 682 will definitely have once been a cat with an assault rifle taped on. Toaster will have catted too.

* I am a Toaster and You are a Fish need to cross paths.

* "An abandoned coal mine found deeper than humans have ever been known to explore." The inspiration for this is obvious. Should be workable.

> **I don't remember the context of this conversation. 
> It probably had to do with Clef's Proposal and Bullet Cat.**
> "This is like the birth of Christianity."
> "Only cooler, and with cats made out of sentient bullets!"
> "Just like Mommy used to makes."

* Cow burning, religious sacrifice. Foundation, your IRC is weird and I love it.

* A hairbrush, that when held, causes nobody in the world to be able to die.

* A hairbrush that brushes away memories.

* A hairbrush that makes you think hairbrushes are anomalous.

* "An animated sapient statue of John Lennon, powered by widespread belief in the ideals of communism. Currently Neutralized." Can't decide whether to make this guy exactly like John Lennon, or make him a really nice guy you kinda feel bad for in the end. *shrugs*

* 682 is run through 914 for some reason and becomes The Hateful Star. The Hateful Star in Foundation Containment, it turns out, is a temporarily displaced 682. This idea makes no sense, but neither does The Hateful Star.

* "A Las Vegas Transit Bus which compels passengers to never want to leave. Passengers will continue to desire to want to get to their destination, but will refuse to leave when prompted. They will show irritation as the hours, days, or even years go by, but they will continue to act as though this is a normal bus ride." I was on a bus once with a person, we both knew we'd be on the bus for just a few minutes, but they were really impatient, and I'd been putting up with their crap all day, and it was annoying. I wished that bus ride would never end, just to make them unhappy.

> **I read the comma aloud while reading a Tale to a friend. This happened.**
> "Agent Comma. He makes the best Toast."
> "Have some delicious Toast."

* "A cartoon pizza, that once you see it, you become unable to physically taste pizza. Upon seeing an image of a pizza, you will taste the pizza."

* Todd in the Shadows as a Joke SCP.

* Twitter as a Joke SCP.

* A tale in-which the SCP Foundation is called to rescue a non-anomalous cat in a tree.

* A tale in-which 682 is finally terminated (No specific method will be given and the researcher who had the honors will be un-named) and the Foundation must deal with the possibility of losing the funding they were being specifically provided for the containment of 682.

[[/tab]]

[[/tabview]]