[[tabview]]

[[tab skull]]

* [*http://www.scp-wiki.net/forum/t-879617/ SCP-XXXX] - A Shoddy Knock-Off

----

[[div style="float:right; margin:0 0em 0em 1em; width:250px; border:0;"]]
||~ [[image https://i.imgur.com/Rtrmtoq.jpg width="250px"]] ||
||~ **SCP-XXXX-1 at acquisition.** ||
[[/div]]

**Item #:** SCP-XXXX

**Object Class:** --Safe-- Euclid

**Special Containment Procedures:** SCP-XXXX-1 is to be stored in a standard containment locker. Testing of SCP-XXXX is only to be conducted within isolated testing enclosures, and is to be observed remotely. There must be at-least one location within testing enclosures that cannot be observed by any personnel before any testing involving SCP-XXXX begins.

Personnel prone to excessive bleeding are not to interact with SCP-XXXX-1, and only D-Class Personnel are permitted to interact with SCP-XXXX-2 during testing. Personnel interacting with SCP-XXXX-2 outside of testing must be equipped with full protective body armor including opaque goggles, and a radio communications system with GPS.

__Due to potential info-hazards__ any information pertaining to SCP-XXXX that would otherwise be sent to members of the Overwatch Council, is to be relayed through the active HMCL.

Neither component of SCP-XXXX is to be cross-experimented with other SCP objects, and personnel are to avoid referencing other SCP objects in the presence of SCP-XXXX-2 whenever possible.

**Description:** SCP-XXXX-1 appears to be the upper half of a human skull with various attached electronic components with casings made of mixtures of copper, iron, and plastic.

Components of note include:

* A rotatable gear-shaped dial embedded in the left orbital cavity. It is theorized that it is supposed to affect the behaviour of SCP-XXXX-2, but it appears to be non-functional.

* An apparatus embedded in the right orbital cavity, attached to tubing that runs through the neuro-cranial cavity. These components are theorized to be linked to SCP-XXXX-2's apparent ability to know the location of SCP-XXXX-1 at all times.

* A large gear embedded an the top right of the cranium with **[DATA EXPUNGED]** in the center, engraved into the bone. This indicates that SCP-XXXX-2 is ███████████, and therefore should not be exposed to SCP-█████.

When SCP-XXXX-1 is exposed to human blood, SCP-XXXX-2 manifests outside of view of any sapient observer, generally close to SCP-XXXX-1. SCP-XXXX-2 has been known to manifest up to ██ miles away from SCP-XXXX-1, in the case of SCP-XXXX-1 being activated in a heavily populated area.

SCP-XXXX-2 appears to be a human child between █ and ██ years of age, wearing a hooded brown rabbit costume. Any sapient entity that observes SCP-XXXX-2 begin to feel emotions of affection toward SCP-XXXX-2, regardless of any previously held opinions of children. Any conscious entity that physically interacts with SCP-XXXX-2 loses consciousness for a varying period of at-least 4 hours. No sapient entity that has survived interaction with SCP-XXXX-2 has been able to recall details about it's face, and digital observation shows the space within SCP-XXXX-2's hood to be a distorted black void.

After SCP-XXXX-2 manifests, it will attempt to embrace any sapient entity able to directly observe itself or SCP-XXXX-1. Once all such entities are unconscious, all digital sources able to observe either component of SCP-XXXX, will momentarily cease to function. SCP-XXXX-2 will then appear to have de-manifested, and all documents and media within ██ meters of SCP-XXXX-1 will have become altered.

* ██% of affected documents consist of content unrelated to the document's original context.

* ██% of affected documents become scrambled, resembling glitches in a computer system.

* █% of documents retain original context, but will be altered in tone and format.

**Addendum XXXX-01:** Upon aquisition of SCP-XXXX-1, the following document was printed on sheet plastic attached to a piece of string loosely draped over the right orbital implant. This document appears to be immune to the data randomization effects of SCP-XXXX-1.

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Document-XXXX-01" hide="[-] Hide Document-XXXX-01"]]

> **Tired of Anomalous Skulls offered by leading brands?**
> Wish they did more than just turn things into **Potato Skins**?
> Well fret not, Foundation researchers! The **Cyber-Skull** is here!
> Just **[Data Expunged]** and let the **Happy Bunny** do the rest!
> 
> [[size 75%]]**Cyber-Skull** and **Happy Bunny** are in no way affiliated with Dr. W█████████████, or related brands.[[/size]]

[[/collapsible]]

It should be noted that the black-boxing and data expungement were not added by the Foundation and appear to be part of the printing.

The reverse side of this document was blank upon acquisition, but currently shows SCP-XXXX's SCP designation number, which was found, printed on the document through unknown means, during initial containment of SCP-XXXX-1. Designation SCP-XXXX-1a pending.

**Addendum XXXX-02:** Agents equipped with protective gear and sufficient blinders were able to safely apprehend SCP-XXXX-2 and bring it to a secure location for interview:

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Interview XXXX" hide="[-] Hide Interview XXXX"]]

> **Interviewer:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1[[footnote]]Placeholder[[/footnote]]
> **Interviewed:** SCP-XXXX-2
>
> **Foreword:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 is blindfolded and separated from SCP-XXXX-2 via glass wall.
> 
> **<Begin Log>**
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "OK, Let's get this started."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Thank you. Where do you come from?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Happy Bunny Sunshine **Rainbow Land!!!**"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "And what relation does Happy... Sunshine... Sparkles... Land? Um. What relation does it have to Dr. Wondertainment?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Happy Bunny is compatible with leading brands!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "I see. And how are you related to SCP-███?
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "Cyber Skull and Happy Bunny are compatible with leading brands!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "This isn't really going anywhere."
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** "I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Thank you, what relationship do you, as in specifically SCP-XXXX-2, have with SCP-XXXX-1?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (distorted):** "......I'm Happy Bunny! I Love You!"
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1:** "Thank you, but please answer the question?"
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (heavily distorted):** "I'm... Happy... Bunny! I... Love... You!"
> 
> **Note:** the next approximately █ minutes of the recording were replaced with a recording of person-of-interest ███████████ ██████, reading what appears to be a driving instruction manual for mooses, excerpt below. ███████████ ██████ has a tenuous grasp on human speech patterns, so dialogue will be transcribed as spoken. 
> 
> **███████████ ██████:** Place your front, little, hoovey-hooves, into, the little, hoovey-holes, on, the steering wheel. Use, your tail, to change gear. Ham sandwich.
> 
> **Note:** After the recording switched back to SCP-XXXX-2 and Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1, both remained silent for █ minutes.
> 
> **Dr. RESEARCHERNAME1 (in apparent distress):** I... I would like to end this interview now. Send in some D-Class or whatever to collect a blood sample, I--
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2 (heavily distorted): HAPPY BUNNY CAN HELP. I //AM// HAPPY BUNNY.**
> 
> **Note:** SCP-XXXX-2 proceeded to materialize a small bladed weapon in it's hand and proceeded to **[DATA EXPUNGED]** covering the floors of the interview enclosure on both sides of the glass wall with approximately █ to ██ meters of it's own blood.
> 
> **<End Log>**

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-03:**

[[collapsible show="[+] Access Limited to Personnel Level 4 and Lower" hide="[-] Level 4 Security Access Granted"]]

> //Analysis of the **copious** blood sample provided by SCP-XXXX-2 have presented a genetic match for the son of O5-█, who went missing on ██/██/████. Bone sampling from SCP-XXXX-1 yields the same. SCP-XXXX was once O5-█'s son.//
> 
> //No member of the Overwatch Council is to be made aware of this. We're going to say it's an info-hazard or something. Information is to be relayed through the HMCL.//
> 
> //We've seen what happens when an O5 gets sentimental about an anomalous object. Rampant favoritism, frequent containment breaches, inconceivable amounts of Foundation resources expended in a futile attempt to cure them.//
> 
> //We've seen this happen, we know how it ends. We don't need another one.// **-O5-██**

[[/collapsible]]

Testing of SCP-XXXX to be suspended.

> //SCP-████ was discovered and contained thanks to SCP-XXXX. We can utilize this.//
> 
> //Besides, it's not like this is the worst Info-Hazard we have.// **-O5-█**

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Experiment Log XXXX" hide="[-] Hide Experiment Log XXXX"]]

> **Experiment #XXXX-001:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME2[[footnote]]Placeholder[[/footnote]]
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-001
> **Items Provided:**
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for approximately 6 hours and later reports discomfort considered typical of sleeping on the floor of a Foundation testing chamber. The labels on D-XXXX-001's standard Class D Personnel uniform now read as different labels, including one printed in Swahili for Mr. BRANDNAME branded snackfoods on D-XXXX-001's pants.

> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3[[footnote]]Placeholder[[/footnote]]
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 copy of the Foundation documentation for SCP-XXXX.
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for 18 hours and later reports feeling well rested despite having a bad dream. Provided documents now appear to be documentation for non-existent SCP-████, complete with acquisition logs and containment procedures. SCP-████ is later acquired in exactly the incident described by the given acquisition log, and is contained in the same way. Researchers writing the official Foundation documentation for SCP-████ wrote a duplicate of the documents provided by SCP-XXXX as their first draft, without prior knowledge of SCP-XXXX.
> 
> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 Copy of the novel "███ █████████ ████, ████████ █████ ████ █████ ██ ████ ███-███ ███████████ ███ ██████"
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject loses consciousness for 4 hours and reports a slight headache. Provided document is found to have become a french picture book appropriate for a standard child's reading level, containing various collages of every visual memetic kill agent known to the Foundation, and was immediately disposed of via incineration.
> 
> **Experiment #XXXX-███:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME3
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 phone book.
> * Blood sample from SCP-XXXX-2, to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result: [Data Expunged]** 
> **Note:** Further testing by this researcher is forbidden by order of O5-██.

> **Experiment #XXXX-365:**
> **Researcher:** Dr. RESEARCHERNAME2
> **Subject:** D-XXXX-███
> **Items Provided:**
> * 1 copy of the ██/██/████ edition of █████'s █████ magazine.
> * Blood sample to activate SCP-XXXX-1
> **Result:** Subject fails to regain consciousness before monthly termination of D Class Personnel. Provided document now appears to match the driving manual read by ███████████ ██████ during Interview XXXX, up to page 27.

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum XXXX-04:**

[[collapsible show="[+] Show Incident Report XXXX-01" hide="[-] Hide Incident Report XXXX-01"]]

During Experiment #███, SCP-XXXX-2 manifested at Site ██ carrying a bladed weapon. Surveillance systems became heavily corrupted and SCP-XXXX-2 could not be consistently tracked. It had terminated at-least ███ personnel and neutralized █ SCP objects of similar description to itself, before a member of personnel was able to announce the presence of SCP-XXXX-2 over the PA system.

> **<Begin Transcript>**
> 
> **Personnel:** Everybody, we have a visit from Happy Bunny Sunshine Rainbow Land!
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** Hi! Everybody, I'm Happy Bunny, I Love You! I'm here to Play!
> 
> **Personnel:** Come play with Happy Bunny, everybody!
> 
> **SCP-XXXX-2:** I Love You!
> 
> **Personnel:** YAAA--!
> 
> **Note:** A stabbing sound was then heard followed by a gurgling noise before the PA system was cut. The body of this member of personnel was never found and they could not be identified from surveillance footage.
> 
> **<End Transcript>**

After agents became aware of the presence of SCP-XXXX-2, suitable equipment was dispersed among personnel and SCP-XXXX-2 was apprehended and brought back to Site ██. Upon being brought in the vicinity of SCP-XXXX-1, **[DATA EXPUNGED]** and appeared to have de-manifested. Later interview indicates that SCP-XXXX-1 had been set to "Play Mode" during this incident, and that it is most often set to "Demo Mode." SCP-XXXX-2 has requested it be set to "Play Mode" more often.

[[/collapsible]]

[[/tab]]

[[tab Notes]]

+ Notes and SCP ideas

* Photo that inspired Happy Bunny was taken with my cellphone while on a cruise. There was a kid walking around the ship in a bear or bunny costume (I don't remember but I hope it turns out to be a bunny, obviously) and they were in the photo, and for some reason you couldn't see their face, and everything else in the picture was distorted, it was really cool. It's probably still on that phone, and I'm pretty sure I still have it, otherwise it seems to be lost.

[[div style="float:right; margin:0 0em 0em 1em; width:250px; border:0;"]]
||~ [[image https://i.imgur.com/G3pcqJ5.jpg width="250px"]] ||
||~ **I have this VHS tape. ||
||~ I don't know what's on it. ||
||~ I don't know what the label means. ||
||~ I don't know where it came from. ||
||~ I must make it an SCP somehow.** ||
[[/div]]

* An SCP just appears in the database one day. It's an indestructibe reality-warper that punches 682 out and punches sharks with ice cream and everybody likes it. It's actually a vaguely-humanoid blob thing that does none of those things, doesn't make you like it, doesn't say or do anything except try to "hang out" with "popular" SCPs and personnel, and it's only anomalous quality is an unstoppable ability to edit it's own entry in the SCP database, save for addendums, which it ignores. It appears to be otherwise non-intelligent and non-sapient.

* "Brain Thrower. A World War II era flame thrower that shoots human brains. Lead to a very confused squadron." I have no strong emotional attachments to this so if I can't figure out what else to do with it that can make it an SCP, I'll just make it an Anomalous Object and be done with it.

* "De-Cat-ifying Chamber: A chamber which turns cats into things that are not cats." I said once I had no intention of making an SCP that was a cat at this time despite being a cat myself, and I meant it. This SCP is __so__ not a cat, it de-cats other cats. Will probably be a Joke SCP with a canon stating that originally, most SCP objects were cats, as opposed to the roughly 2% cats are currently, and they were de-cat-ified to break up the monotony. 682 will definitely have once been a cat with an assault rifle taped on. Toaster will have catted too.

* I am a Toaster and You are a Fish need to cross paths.

* "An abandoned coal mine found deeper than humans have ever been known to explore." The inspiration for this is obvious. Should be workable.

> **I don't remember the context of this conversation. 
> It probably had to do with Clef's Proposal and Bullet Cat.**
> "This is like the birth of Christianity."
> "Only cooler, and with cats made out of sentient bullets!"
> "Just like Mommy used to makes."

* Cow burning, religious sacrifice. Foundation, your IRC is weird and I love it.

* A hairbrush, that when held, causes nobody in the world to be able to die.

* A hairbrush that brushes away memories.

* A hairbrush that makes you think hairbrushes are anomalous.

* "An animated sapient statue of John Lennon, powered by widespread belief in the ideals of communism. Currently Neutralized." Can't decide whether to make this guy exactly like John Lennon, or make him a really nice guy you kinda feel bad for in the end. *shrugs*

* 682 is run through 914 for some reason and becomes The Hateful Star. The Hateful Star in Foundation Containment, it turns out, is a temporarily displaced 682. This idea makes no sense, but neither does The Hateful Star.

* "A Las Vegas Transit Bus which compels passengers to never want to leave. Passengers will continue to desire to want to get to their destination, but will refuse to leave when prompted. They will show irritation as the hours, days, or even years go by, but they will continue to act as though this is a normal bus ride." I was on a bus once with a person, we both knew we'd be on the bus for just a few minutes, but they were really impatient, and I'd been putting up with their crap all day, and it was annoying. I wished that bus ride would never end, just to make them unhappy.

> **I read the comma aloud while reading a Tale to a friend. This happened.**
> "Agent Comma. He makes the best Toast."
> "Have some delicious Toast."

* "A cartoon pizza, that once you see it, you become unable to physically taste pizza. Upon seeing an image of a pizza, you will taste the pizza."

* Todd in the Shadows as a Joke SCP.

* Twitter as a Joke SCP.

* A tale in-which the SCP Foundation is called to rescue a non-anomalous cat in a tree.

* A tale in-which 682 is finally terminated (No specific method will be given and the researcher who had the honors will be un-named) and the Foundation must deal with the possibility of losing the funding they were being specifically provided for the containment of 682.

[[/tab]]

[[/tabview]]