**Item #:** SCP-BT64

**Object Class:** Euclid

**Special Containment Procedures:** At no time should SCP-BT64 be housed in any Foundation facility. SCP-BT64 is to be contained at all times in an isolated civilian dwelling of low value, suitable for the habitation of one humanoid. SCP-BT64 is to be provided with meals and clothing it has the lowest preference for. Except for the purposes of testing, any other request made by SCP-BT64 is to be rejected without review. SCP-BT64 is to be submitted to ongoing weekly psychological examination to evaluate whether it has started to develop any emotional attachment to any part of it's containment procedures. If emotional attachment of any kind is found, SCP-BT64 is to be administered Class B Amnesiacs. 

SCP-BT64 is be closely monitored by personnel to ensure that it does not engage in self-harm. 

While there are no immediate plans, no termination attempts of SCP-BT64 are to be attempted or theorized by any Foundation personnel. Any efforts made to decommission SCP-BT64 must first be focused on neutralizing it's effects in a non-harmful manner.

Any personnel interacting with SCP-BT64 must read, understand and sign document BT64-01 to further limit its effects. The orders in document BT64-01 may not be countermanded under any circumstance. Any other personnel wishing to sign document BT64-01 for their own protection may do so.

**Description:** SCP-BT64 resembles a middle aged human male of **[Redacted]** descent, previously known as **[Redacted]**. Until exposure to SCP-████, it held the position of ████ within the Foundation. SCP-BT64 appears to be in reasonable health with exception to early indicators of a heart condition.

SCP-BT64 has two anomalous properties:

If SCP-BT64 should ever --claim legal ownership-- feel a sense of ownership or belonging of any --tangible-- object including currency, property, goods, corporate paraphernalia, live animals, or live personnel, that object will dematerialize.

All attempts to locate objects or personnel that have dematerialized due to the effect of SCP-BT64 have failed, including use of GPS systems and radio isotope tracking markers. Tracking experiments involving **[DATA EXPUNGED]** have proven inclusive, leading to the conclusion that affected objects simply cease to exist.

Any entity with intention to harm SCP-BT64 will be inflicted with an incident to themselves that is both proportional to the harm intended to SCP-BT64, and sufficient to prevent harm to SCP-BT64. This effect does not appear to be limited by distance, and appears to be influenced purely by intent. Any indirect attempts to harm SCP-BT64, such as one party ordering another party to cause harm to SCP-BT64, will result in SCP-BT64 effecting both parties.

Accidental harm has not been demonstrated to be prevented by this effect, though it should be noted that as of ██/██/████, SCP-BT64 has suffered no injuries since initial containment, other than those caused by it's own actions.

**Acquisition Log:** SCP-BT64 was created accidentally at Site ██ during a large scale containment breach involving SCP-████ and group of interest **[Data Expunged]**. The group was believed to be involved in an assassination attempt of former ████, now designated SCP-BT64. According to surviving surveillance footage, just before the assassination group had made their way to SCP-BT64's office, SCP-████ manifested itself before SCP-BT64, reportedly offering to protect it from termination "for a price."^^//[[span style="color:#BB0011"]][Sic][[/span]]//^^ Panicked, SCP-BT64 begged SCP-████ to "Please, just take everything!"^^//[[span style="color:#BB0011"]][Sic][[/span]]//^^ It was then found that Site ██, along with all sites under the jurisdiction of ████, and all contained SCP objects and personnel, had vanished. On review of the surveillance footage, ████ was immediately removed from employment and re-designated SCP-BT64.

[[collapsible show="[+] Interview Log BT64-5: O5 Approval Required" hide="[-] Access Granted"]]
Interview takes place on ██/██/████, the day after acquisition.

> **Doctor Tog:** Good Morning SCP-BT64 shall we begin?
> 
> **SCP-BT64:** Huh, funny how fast I became BT64, used to be you would call me sir.
> 
> **Doctor Tog:** Yes BT64, I believe it was you that wrote that particular page of the manual. So tell me, how did this whole vanishing items situation begin.
> 
> **SCP-BT64:** I guess you haven't seen the docs on 1065, hasn't been written up yet? No, wouldn't want everyone to know we can't put something in a box.
> 
> **Doctor Tog:** I have been read in on 1065, I'd just like your own thoughts on this.
> 
> **SCP-BT64:** Well then, you know 1065 is a reality bender of some kind that we are having exceptional difficulty pinning down. He seems to offer services as a bodyguard, except eventually his clients always get assassinated. He came to me a week ago and told me I was going to be killed and asked me to pay him to be my bodyguard. You've read the file, the more you give, the longer you live. I wasn't sure I wanted a shadow the rest of my life, but I did want to live. So I told him "take everything". I'm not dead and we both know what happened to the fool with the sniper rifle.
> 
> **Doctor Tog:** Backfire explosion, 1 in a million chance apparently.
> 
> **SCP-BT64:** Exactly.
> 
> Interview ends
> 

[[/collapsible]]

**Addendum:** After approximately 3 months of the foundation containing SCP-BT64 at ███ ███████ ███ ████████, ███ █████████ , wholly owned by the foundation, the entire dwelling and the majority of it's contents dematerialised, replaced by a vacant lot with recent signs of demolition and a neatly folded pile of SCP-BT64's uniforms. After incident review concluded that SCP-BT64 had developed an attachment to the dwelling and had formed an emotional attachment to it as his "home". 


Document BT64-01

------Begin read only segment-------

> By order of 05 Command, collectively and singularly, all orders contained in the read only segment of this document my not be countermanded by any member of the SCP Foundation including but not limited to 05 Personnel.
> 
> The below listed personnel are ordered to never do harm to SCP-BT64.
> 
> The below listed personnel acknowledge and declare that any request or order they make that may be interpretted as meaning harm to SCP-BT64 is not to be obeyed under any circumstance. Any action taken to harm SCP-BT64 is explicitly without the consent of the below listed personnel.
> 
> Signed - 
> 
> Doctor Bane Tog

------End read only segment------